olacabs.com 2011-01-14

# Book Cabs and Car Rentals Online

  Payment Related 

Q: What are the different modes of payment you support?  
A: We accept all major credit and debit cards. We also accept Cash Cards and Net Banking. In details, we accept the following:  
**Credit Cards:** MasterCard, Visa, Diners Club  
**Debit Cards and Cash Cards:** ABN-AMRO, Andhra Bank, Axis Bank, Bank of Baroda, Bank of India, The Bank of Punjab, Barclays, Canara Bank, Central Bank of India, Citibank, Corporation Bank, Dena Bank, Deutsche Bank, HDFC Bank, HSBC, ICICI Bank, IDBI Bank, Indian Bank, Indian Overseas Bank, IndusInd Bank, ING Vysya, Karnataka Bank, Karur Vysya Bank, Lakshmi Vilas Bank, Punjab National Bank, South Indian Bank, Standard Chartered, State Bank of India, Syndicate Bank, Federal Bank, Union Bank of India, YES Bank, ItzCash  
**Net Banking:** Axis Bank, Citibank, Federal Bank, HDFC Bank, ICICI Bank, J&K Bank, State Bank of India 

Q: Can I buy for someone else using my credit/debit card?  
A: Yes definitely! You need to mention the card holder details for the card payment but you can enter anyone's name for the car booking. 

Q: Is it safe to use my credit/debit card on your site? Do you store my card number and details?  
A: It is completely safe to use our site. We have partnered with EBS for the payment gateway. EBS provides a 128-bit SSL encryption technology compliant solution which is certified by VeriSign. We don't store any card details. 

  Bookings Related 

Q: Can I book a cab from you without paying online?  
A: Yes! You can call us and we will book a cab for you on Phone! We will collect money from you on delivery of the car rental voucher. There is an extra charge of Rs. 30 for this. 

Q: Do I need to register on your site to book tickets?  
A: No. You can use our service fully without the need to register. You just need to provide your details at the time of booking. 

Q: What if the car doesn't show up?  
A: In case the vehicle you booked doesn't show up, we will offer you a full refund immediately. 

Q: What if the car shows up late?  
A: We try our best to ensure our partners reach our customers on time. But in case of delays, do call us and we will help you out by either providing an alternate vehicle or giving you a full refund. 

  Cancellations Related 

Q: Can I change my booking?  
A: Yes. You can change the date of booking till 2 days before the booked date free of charge. After that, there will be a cancellation charge as detailed in the next question. 

Q: How do I cancel my booking? What are the charges?  
A: You can cancel your booking anytime. The cancellation charges are as follows:  
48 hours before booked time: No Charge  
24 - 48 hours before booked time: 20% of the booking amount  
0 - 24 hours before booked time: 50% of the booking amount

  Terms and Conditions 

Welcome to our website. If you continue to browse and use this website you are agreeing to comply with and be bound by the following terms and conditions of use, which together with our privacy policy govern ANI Technologies' (Owner of Olacabs.com) relationship with you in relation to this website.

The term 'Olacabs.com' or 'us' or 'we' refers to the owner of the website whose registered office is 33-G, Bhai Randhir Singh Nagar, Ludhiana, Punjab 141001, India. Our company registration number is U72900PB2010PTC034472, registered at Chandigarh. The term 'you' refers to the user or viewer of our website.

The use of this website is subject to the following terms of use:

  * The content of the pages of this website is for your general information and use only. It is subject to change without notice. 
  * Neither we nor any third parties provide any warranty or guarantee as to the accuracy, timeliness, performance, completeness or suitability of the information and materials found or offered on this website for any particular purpose. You acknowledge that such information and materials may contain inaccuracies or errors and we expressly exclude liability for any such inaccuracies or errors to the fullest extent permitted by law. 
  * Your use of any information or materials on this website is entirely at your own risk, for which we shall not be liable. It shall be your own responsibility to ensure that any products, services or information available through this website meet your specific requirements. 
  * This website contains material which is owned by or licensed to us. This material includes, but is not limited to, the design, layout, look, appearance and graphics. Reproduction is prohibited other than in accordance with the copyright notice, which forms part of these terms and conditions. 
  * All trade marks reproduced in this website which are not the property of, or licensed to, the operator are acknowledged on the website. 
  * Unauthorized use of this website may give rise to a claim for damages and/or be a criminal offense. 
  * From time to time this website may also include links to other websites. These links are provided for your convenience to provide further information. They do not signify that we endorse the website(s). We have no responsibility for the content of the linked website(s). 
  * You may not create a link to this website from another website or document without Olacabs's prior written consent. 
  * Your use of this website and any dispute arising out of such use of the website is subject to the laws of India or other regulatory authority. 

  Disclaimer 

The information contained in this website is for general information purposes only. The information is provided by Olacabs and while we endeavor to keep the information up to date and correct, we make no representations or warranties of any kind, express or implied, about the completeness, accuracy, reliability, suitability or availability with respect to the website or the information, products, services, or related graphics contained on the website for any purpose. Any reliance you place on such information is therefore strictly at your own risk.

In no event will we be liable for any loss or damage including without limitation, indirect or consequential loss or damage, or any loss or damage whatsoever arising from loss of data or profits arising out of, or in connection with, the use of this website.

Through this website you are able to link to other websites which are not under the control of Olacabs. We have no control over the nature, content and availability of those sites. The inclusion of any links does not necessarily imply a recommendation or endorse the views expressed within them.

Every effort is made to keep the website up and running smoothly. However, Olacabs takes no responsibility for, and will not be liable for, the website being temporarily unavailable due to technical issues beyond our control.

  Privacy Policy 

This privacy policy sets out how Olacabs uses and protects any information that you give Olacabs when you use this website.

Olacabs is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.

Olacabs may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from 3rd December 2010.

**What we collect**  
We may collect the following information: 

  * name and job title 
  * contact information including email address 
  * demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests 
  * other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers 

**What we do with the information we gather**  
We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons: 

  * Internal record keeping. 
  * We may use the information to improve our products and services. 
  * We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided. 
  * From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail. We may use the information to customize the website according to your interests. 

**Security**  
We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

**How we use cookies**  
A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyze web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyze data about webpage traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.

You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

**Links to other websites**  
Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.

You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998. A small fee will be payable. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please write to support@olatrip.com.

If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible, at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.

**Contacting Us**  
If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information on the Contact Us page.
